mtcgame.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy & Cookies

MTCGAME knows that you care about your privacy and the use of your personal information. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you from any source and in any way – through our Websites, applications or other Internet based interactions, in our retail stores.

We Gather the Following Personal Information About Guests:

Information That You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Websites or that you give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but this will limit your ability to purchase products offered on the Websites, or to take advantage of some features or promotions.

When you place an order with us online, in a store or in any other way, your contact information is used to communicate related information, such as order and shipment confirmation, release date changes and requests for more information to facilitate processing your order. You may opt-out of these communications by canceling your order.

We obtain information about you when you search, buy, participate in a contest or questionnaire, , or otherwise contact us or post information on our Websites. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order through a Website or provide information to update or create your account with us (you may have more than one account if you have used more than one email address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, email, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; create any wish or gift list; participate in any forums or discussion areas or product reviews; or create any alerts or other email notification services we may offer now or in the future. The information collected typically includes your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; content of reviews you may provide; emails to us; and any other personal information that you provide to us or post on the Websites.

The information we receive or can determine from your interaction with our Websites includes your Internet (IP) address; login and password information; email address; web browser type and version; preferred language; geographic location using IP address or the GPS, wireless, or Bluetooth technology on your device; operating system and computer platform; purchase history, which we may aggregate with similar information from other guests or keep in non-aggregated form; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Websites, including date and time; one or more unique identifiers; products you viewed or searched for; areas of our Websites you visited; and the phone number you used to call our toll-free number. We also may log the length of time of your visit and the number of times you visit and purchase from us. We assign you one or more unique identifiers to help keep track of your future visits.

Mobile location services: Certain stores may also collect and use location information from mobile devices. Location information allows us to learn more about how guests use our stores to enhance the guest experience and, in certain circumstances, deliver push notifications and other content to your mobile device when you are near, enter and move through our stores, and send or provide you with offers and promotional information that we believe may be of interest to you. You may prevent or limit collection of location information by turning off your mobile device or antennas, such as WiFi or Bluetooth, and opting out of location services on your device.
